cs-cart.com 2013-04-02

# Resources :: Privacy Policy -

This privacy policy (the “Policy”) applies to all personal information that Simbirsk Technology Ltd. (the “Company”) can receive from the User during the period of the User's staying at the website [http://www.cs-cart.com](http://www.cs-cart.com/) and its subdomains (the “Website”). And the Policy describes how the Company collects, uses and discloses the personal information obtained through the Website.

By using the Website, the User agrees that the Company can collect and use his personal information.

The User can visit the Website without disclosing his personal information, but in the cases when the User has decided to request certain information, use the services or purchase the Products (any software developed by the Company and distributed on the Website), the Company may ask the User to provide his personal information.

The Company has a right to ask the User to provide the following information: the first name and last name, the name of the company that he represents (if any), home or office address, telephone number, email address as well as financial and other information that is specified on the Website.

Any information that is automatically collected as a result of the User's visiting the Website, including the order in which the Website pages are visited, is not intended for identifying individual users. The Company uses “cookies” to make the Website more user-friendly.

The Company uses the User's personal information to provide products and services, resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems, increase usability and improve the Website, and inform the User of new services and products. When the User registers at the Website, he automatically agrees that he may receive certain information from the Company, such as the information about the services, updates or new Products as well as other information which the Company may consider important to inform about.

The Company does not sell or disclose personal information about the User. The Company may disclose and transfer personal information to third parties only if required by the Russian or international law and/or authorities in accordance with legal procedure.

If the User is registered at the Website, he can access, review and modify his personal information at any time. In order to edit his personal information, the User has to log in to his profile page on the Website (at <http://www.cs-cart.com/helpdesk> or [http://forum.cs-cart.com](http://forum.cs-cart.com/)).

The Website contains links to third party websites. However, the Company has no control over these websites or their privacy practices. Before submitting personal information on these websites, the Company encourages the User to carefully review their privacy policies.

The Company uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect the User's personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification. However, the information that is transferred or stored on the Internet cannot be guarded perfectly, so the Company makes no guarantees of the absolute security of personal information.

The Company has a right to amend this Privacy Policy. In the event of amendment, the Company publics all changes or additions to this Privacy Policy on the Website. The User's continued use of the Company Products will constitute his acceptance of new terms of this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions about this statement, please contact us by using our [contact form](http://www.cs-cart.com/send-message.html).
